Women's Building; Records apap292
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Resource File, 1954-2000, Undated; 3; 5 cubic ft.
  - Speakout, 1973 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 9)
  - Speakout, 1974 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 10)
  - Speakout, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 11)
  - Speakout, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 12)
  - Speakout, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 13)
  - Speakout, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 14)
  - Speakout, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 15)
  - Speakout, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 16)
  - Speakout, 1977 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 17)
  - Theatre Group/Events/Etc., Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 18)
  - Spirited Woman, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 19)
  - State of New York Executive Department Division of Human Rights, Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 20)
  - Support, Counseling, 1984; 1985; 1986; 1987; 1988 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 21)
  - Title IX, 1972; 1974 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 22)
  - Transsexuals, Transvestites, Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 23)
  - Unitarian Women's Group - Newsletters, 1983 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 24)
  - United Fruit, 1973 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 25)
  - Upper Hudson Planned Parenthood, 1983 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 26)
  - VD Handbook, Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 27)
  - Wallflower Order, Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 28)
  - The Washington Park Spirit, 1972 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 29)
  - Weather Underground, 1975-1976 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 30)
  - The Woman Activist, 1973; 1974 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 31)
  - Women and Ageism, 1978; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 32)
  - Woman Alive - Honolulu, Hawaii, 1975 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 33)
  - Woman and Art, 1977; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 34)
  - Woman's Art Information, 1979 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 35)
  - Women - Asian-American, 1976 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 36)
  - Women: A Berkshire Feminist News Journal, 1974; 1975 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 37)
  - Women: A Berkshire Feminist News Journal, 1975; 1976 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 38)
  - The Women's Building, Inc., 1985; 1989; 1991; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 39)
  - Women in Business Directory, Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 40)
  - Women's Center, 1975; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 41)
  - Women's Connection, 1984; 1985 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 42)
  - Women and Crime, Report of National Conference held February 1976, 1986 February (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 43)
  - Women's Culture/Art/Music, 1983; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 44)
  - Women in Education, 1977; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 45)
  - Women's and Employment, 1975; 1977; 1978; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 46)
  - Women's Equity Action League Newsletter, 1973; 1974 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 47)
  - Women's Films, 1973; 1977; 1979; 1980; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 48)
  - Women's Films, 1975; 1977; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 49)
  - The Women's Foundation Newsletter, 1988-1989 (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 50)
  - Women's Group - Other Cities, 1981; 1982; 1983; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 51)
  - Women's Health, 1971; 1979; Undated (Box 4 (3-Resource File), Folder 52)
  - Women's Health, 1973; 1977; 1978; 1979; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 1)
  - Women's Health, 1979; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 2)
  - Women's Health Group, 1984 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 3)
  - Women's Health Care, 1976; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 4)
  - Women - Hispanic Americans, 1977 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 5)
  - Women in History, 1973; 1977; 1978 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 6)
  - Women in Struggle - Newsletters, 1973 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 7)
  - Women In Struggle, 1975 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 8)
  - Women's Information Center News, 1980 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 9)
  - Women and Law, 1973; 1975; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 10)
  - Women Learning Resources and Supportive Sources, 1978 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 11)
  - Women Literature and Culture, 1984; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 12)
  - Women Make Movies, Inc., 1984 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 13)
  - Women in Management, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 14)
  - Women and The Media, 1975; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 15)
  - Women and Militarism, ca. 1982 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 16)
  - Women's Movement, 1977; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 17)
  - Women - Myths and Images, 1971; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 18)
  - Women New York - the Women's Division of the State of New York, 1976 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 19)
  - Women Parenting, Legal and Medical, 1990; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 20)
  - Women's Peace Encampment, 1983 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 21)
  - The Women's Picnic, 1997 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 22)
  - Women's Politics, 1973; 1977; 1978 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 23)
  - Women and Psychology, 1970; 1977; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 24)
  - Women's Resource Directory - A Work in Progress, Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 25)
  - Women and Religion, 1977; 1978 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 26)
  - Women's Resorts, 1976; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 27)
  - Women's Resorts, 1982; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 28)
  - Women's Rights Events, 1970s; 1979 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 29)
  - Women's Rights Events, 1980s (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 30)
  - Women's Rights Events, 1990s (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 31)
  - Women's Rights Events, 1990s (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 32)
  - Women's Rights Events, 1990s (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 33)
  - Women's Rights Events, 1990s (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 34)
  - Women and Sexism, 1977; 1978; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 35)
  - Women and Sexuality, 1971; 1976; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 36)
  - Women in Sports, 1977; 1978 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 37)
  - Women Theory and Analyses, 1976; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 38)
  - Women Together: The Journal of North Country Women, 1979 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 39)
  - Women and Violence, 1971; 1977; 1978; Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 40)
  - Women Writing Newsletters, Undated (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 41)
  - Womenergy: Women for an Oneonta Women's Center, 1980 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 42)
  - Woman Power - A monthly Report on Fair Employment Practices for Women, 1974 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 43)
  - WWAC News -Washington Women's Art Center, 1980; 1981 (Box 5 (3-Resource File), Folder 44)
- Related Groups and Tenants, 1969-1997, Undated; 4; 0.75 cubic ft.
  This series includes material concerning the tenants of the Women's Building and groups that had an explicit relationship with the Women's Building or Tri-City Women's Center. This consists of material not particular to the Women's Building or Tri-City Women's Center, including correspondence, leases and other agreements, promotional material, newsletters and other publications, and general administrative documents.
  - Albany Area National Organization for Women Lease, 1990; 1992; 1993 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 1)
  - Alexandria Douglas- Albany Women's Forum, 1978; Undated (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 2)
  - Allison Chiropractic, 1997 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 3)
  - ATHENA, 1975; 1976 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 4)
  - Association of Independent Living Centers - Lease, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 5)
  - Capital District Citizens for Access, 1992 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 6)
  - Capital District Women, 1969; 1970; 1971 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 7)
  - Capital District Woman's Political Caucus, 1983 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 8)
  - Capital District Women's Building Association Legal Project, Incorporation, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 9)
  - Committee for a New Korea Policy, 1982; 1983; 1984 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 10)
  - Community Resolution Program, New York State, 1983 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 11)
  - Chicago Women's Liberation Union, 1973; Undated (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 12)
  - COSMEP: Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers, 1973; 1974; 1975; 1976 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 13)
  - COSMEP: Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers, 1974 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 14)
  - COSMEP: Committee of Small Magazine Editors and Publishers- Newsletters and Other Items, 1974; 1975 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 15)
  - A Discovery of Ourselves As Women Celebration '74 - Skidmore College, 1974; Undated (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 16)
  - Maat Dompin: The Womyn of Color Land Project, Undated (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 17)
  - Alexandria Douglas - Albany County Rape Crisis Center, 1976; 1977 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 18)
  - Alexandria Douglas - Alternative Week Schedules, 1976; 1977; 1978 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 19)
  - Alexandria Douglas - Executive Order 40+ Affirmative Action, 1978; Undated (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 20)
  - Alexandria Douglas - New York State Center for Women in Government, 1979 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 21)
  - Empire State Pride Agenda - Lease, 1991; 1992 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 22)
  - Enterprising Women's Leadership Institute, 1998 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 23)
  - Family and Child Care Association of New York State, 1996 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 24)
  - Female Fitness - Lease, 1994; 1996; 1997; 1998 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 25)
  - Robin Findlay, 1989 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 26)
  - Gay and Lesbian Alliance - Northampton, Massechusetts, 1983 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 27)
  - Herizons - Binghamton, New York Women's Club, 1983; 1984; 1985 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 28)
  - Holiday Our Own - Lease, 1992; 1993; 1997 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 29)
  - Legal Aid Society, 1985; 1989 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 30)
  - Joann Little - Feminist Alliance Against Rape, 1974 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 31)
  - National Gay Task Force, 1974; 1976; 1977; 1978 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 32)
  - New York State Coalition Against Sexual Assault, 1992; 1993 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 33)
  - Social Action Center, 1982; 1983 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 34)
  - Speakout, 1972 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 35)
  - Speakout - Form Letters, 1976; Undated (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 36)
  - Speakout - Requests, 1977; 1978 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 37)
  - Speakout - Subscription Labels, Undated (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 38)
  - Speakout - Workers "Exchange" File, 1975; 1976; 1977; 1980; Undated (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 39)
  - State University of New York - Plaza Women's Forum, Undated (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 40)
  - Tri-City Council of Women, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 41)
  - Upstate New York Women's History Conference, 1978 (Box 1 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 42)
  - Women Against Media Violence Against Women, 1977; 1981 (Box 2 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 43)
  - Women's Craft Store (Art and Desire), 1995 (Box 2 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 44)
  - Women's Hall of Fame, 1984; 1987; Undated (Box 2 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 45)
  - Women Outdoors, Undated (Box 2 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 46)
  - A Women's Place, 1976; 1977; Undated (Box 2 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 47)
  - A Women's Place, 1980 (Box 2 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 48)
  - Women's Political Caucus, 1994; 1996 (Box 2 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 49)
  - YWCA - Meeting, 1983-1986 (Box 2 (4-Related Groups and Tenants), Folder 50)
- Publications, 1978-1993, Undated; 5; 0.3 cubic ft.
  Alphabetically by publication title, then chronologically
  The Publications series consists of the published newsletters produced by either the Tri-City Women's Center or the Women's Building. The publication was originally called the Tri-City Women's Center Newsletter, and was renamed first, The Women-Centered News, and then the Women's Building News.
  - Health Series Press Releases and Brochures, Undated (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 51)
  - Women's Center Newsletter, 1978 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 52)
  - Women's Center Newsletter, 1979 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 53)
  - Women's Center Newsletter, 1980 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 54)
  - Women's Center Newsletter, 1981 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 55)
  - Women's Center Newsletter, 1982 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 56)
  - Women's Center Newsletter, 1983 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 57)
  - The Women-Centered News, 1985 June (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 58)
  - The Women-Centered News, 1985 September (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 59)
  - The Women-Centered News, 1986 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 60)
  - The Women-Centered News - Administrative Material, 1990 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 61)
  - The Women-Centered News, 1987; 1988 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 62)
  - The Women-Centered News, 1988; 1989 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 63)
  - The Women-Centered News, 1989 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 64)
  - The Women-Centered News, 1990; 1991; 1993 (Box 1 (5-Publications), Folder 65)